sgforums.com 2019-01-16

# Privacy Policy

At sgForums, we recognise that privacy is important, and this document outlines our privacy policy. 

If you have an enquiry or concern about our privacy policy, pleasecontact us. 

## Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access

You can access our Web site home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data. 

## The services and links of our Web site

Our Web site enables you to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others. When you do so, other visitors may collect your data. 

Our Web site also includes links to a third party Web service providers. Such third party Web service providers may collect personal data about our visitors. 

## Automatic Collection of Information

We automatically log personal data by means such as programming or we link information automatically logged by such means with personal data about specific individuals. We do so for the following purposes: 

  * Technical administration of the Web site
  * Research and development
  * Customer administration
  * Marketing

We use cookies to store personal data or we link information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals. We do so for the following purposes: 

  * Technical administration of the Web site

## Data Collection and Purpose Specification

We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services. 

We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organisations. 

We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than for: 

  * Customer administration
  * Marketing

If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, we offer you the means to consent to this new purpose: by indicating in a box at the point on the site where personal data is collected 

## Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal data from children. 

We take specific steps to protect the privacy of children by: 

  * making reasonable efforts to ensure that a parent has authorised the collection of the child's personal data 

We do provide information about our personal data practices in relation to children on our home page and wherever we knowingly collect personal data from children on our Web site. 

## Disclosure and Visitor Choice

We disclose our visitors' personal data to our subsidiaries or other organisations only for the purposes below: 

  * Customer administration

Where we disclose your personal data for purposes which are different from those indicated in the table mentioned above, we offer you the opportunity to consent to disclosure: 

  * by indicating in a box at the point on the site where personal data is collected 

## Confidentiality / Security

We give you the option of using a secure transmission method to send us the following types of personal data: 

  * primary personal data (such as name and contact details) 
  * other personal and profiling data (such as physical description, leisure activities) 
  * identifiers (such as credit card details, Web site password) 
  * specific personal data (such as racial or ethnic origin, religious beliefs, medical data) 

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from: 

  * unauthorised access
  * improper use or disclosure
  * unauthorised modification
  * unlawful destruction or accidental loss

All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data. 

We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation. 

## Access to the personal data we may hold about you

You can ask us, by contacting us whether we are keeping personal data about you. 

Upon request, which you can indicate bycontacting us. We will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you, within a week. - although we may before require proof of your identity. We will provide the information without any charge. 

We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data: 

  * erased
  * rectified or amended
  * completed

We reserve the right to refuse to provide our visitors with a copy of their personal data, but will give reasons for our refusal. 

We do, however, allow you to challenge our decision to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data. 

## Privacy Support

If you have an enquiry or concern about our privacy policy, pleasecontact us.
